{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Evangelion Trivia",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "Custom Deck",
      "description": "Custom deck description detailing deck's contents.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "asdasd",
      "description": "asdasd"
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Hoe many eyes does Lilith's mask have?",
      "back": "Seven",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "Who invented the concept of AT fields?",
      "back": "Sigmund Fried",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "What are the main antogonists of the series?",
      "back": "Angels",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "How many MAGI computers are at NERV?",
      "back": "Three",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "Where was Adam found?",
      "back": "Antarctica",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "front": "1+1",
      "back": "2",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "example question",
      "back": "example answer",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "b",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "asdas",
      "back": "asdasd",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "front": "asdasda",
      "back": "asdasd",
      "deckId": 3
    }
  ]
}